const DUMMY_DATA = [
  {
    question: "Leaders",
    answer: "scoups",
  },
  {
    question: "angel",
    answer: "jeonghan",
  },
  {
    question: "sunday morning",
    answer: "joshua",
  },
  {
    question: "2nd",
    answer: "jun",
  },
  {
    question: "tiger",
    answer: "hoshi",
  },
  {
    question: "game boi",
    answer: "wonwoo",
  },
  {
    question: "composser",
    answer: "woozi",
  },
  {
    question: "b-boy",
    answer: "the8",
  },
  {
    question: "cook",
    answer: "mingyu",
  },
  {
    question: "being happy virus",
    answer: "dk",
  },
  {
    question: "mc",
    answer: "seungkwan",
  },
  {
    question: "de caprio",
    answer: "vernon",
  },
  {
    question: "kpop future",
    answer: "dino",
  },
];

export { DUMMY_DATA };
